

CONTACT ME

House no. DN- 103/B , Sector 4/A, Khayaban e Sir Syed, Rawalpindi

numananwar789@gmail.com

+92-3325548599

https://numananwar-e1586.web.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/numan-anwar/

https://github.com/numananwar789

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

Pashto

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

PHP Framework (Laravel)

WordPress

Codeignitor

Numan Anwar

Web Designer & Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a Laravel developer with 1 year of experience in the field of software engineering. I have studied software engineering and have gained skills in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, and Laravel. I enjoy reading, coding, and playing cricket.

EXPERIENCE

Final Year Project

2021 - 2022

I have done FYP Project in PHP Framework (Laravel). Which is about Medicine Distribution Management. This project allows distributors to get order online and deliver it.

Laravel Developer

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

I have 3 months of experience as a Laravel Developer in <u>Alright Tech Private Limited</u>. Developed software using the Laravel framework. Handled user authentication and authorization. Implemented CRUD operations for data entry and retrieval. Created RESTful API endpoints for a Laravel application.

PHP Developer

Mar 2023 - Present

I am working as a PHP Codeignitor developer in the Lala Group of Companies. I maintain and develop the company website and add new features to the company website.

EDUCATION

SSC

Govt. Centennial Model For Boys Bannu 2014 - 2016

HSSC

Govt. Post Graduate College Bannu 2016 - 2018

BSc Software Engineering

University of Science and Technology Bannu

2018 - 2022